DELIVERANCE TIME
Offering the prayer of faith in accordance with the book of James 5:16 and Acts 4:30,
Wise Man Daniel is used as an instrument of deliverance in the hands of the Holy Spirit.
As he is moved through the auditorium, on meeting this man, the fire of the Holy Ghost falls upon him,
and the demonic entity behind his setback and affliction is exposed and arrested.
Witness this inspiring deliverance as this man encounters Wise Man Daniel.
Can you speak? Who are you?
I am the idols of his father's house.
What have you done to him?
I am killing him little by little.
You are killing him little by little?
Yes.
He is a preacher of the Gospel.
He is a preacher of the Gospel?
Yes.
What have you done to him?
He is a stubborn person; we have decided to frustrate him.
For four hundred and something years, we have been in his father's house.
He decided to break the yoke by becoming the first born-again.
He has been a thorn in our flesh.
We are from the kingdom, the sanctum of darkness.
That is where we come from.
He gathered some people and they came to his father's house to trouble us.
While they were praying, his prayer was different and so,
we decided that we are going to disgrace him by frustrating him.
In the beginning of his life when he wanted to get married, we delivered a wife unto him.
He is a man who likes beautiful women, so we gave him a beautiful woman.
We gave the woman a heart of stone, so that whatsoever he does or says would not appeal to her.
We decided to fight him from the inside.
He is an associate pastor.
He has gone from one ministry to the other.
We decided that we would frustrate him and all his ventures.
From one place to another, we have always been tele-guiding him.
But he has always been praying and asking God when this affliction would be over.
His father and forefathers have dedicated him, even before his birth.
Every time, his father renews the covenant we have with him.
All the other children of his father are still in our captivity.
But this one has been stubborn towards us.
He still wants to deliver the rest of his brothers.
He led his mother to Christ and we are not happy about that.
He is also working hard to make sure that his father departs from our kingdom but we are saying, "No".
If we don’t destroy him from the inside, we will never get him.
But we don’t know how he managed to locate this place.
What is wrong with this place that you don’t like?
Everybody knows what is wrong with this place.
The fires are too much.
Deliverance at the SCOAN
What does the fire do to your kingdom?
Immediately your hand touched his head, you ignited the fire that was quenched before and
strong roots of our tree inside him began to fall.
The fire is too much.
We tried to frustrate him this morning not to come, igniting a quarrel between him and his wife this morning
so that he would not be able to come here.
Were you sleeping when he came here?
We didn’t know it was going to work out.
A mighty hand held his wrist and drew him into this place against our wish.
Which hand was that?
We don’t know where the hand came from but we know that hand is a very strong hand.
Does it mean you people cannot resist that hand?
The hand is so strong and looks like the hand of a great lion.
There is fire in the fingers of the lion.
When the hand held him, we were surprised because it was a strange appearance.
Right now, it is time you go.
Come out!
Out, you demon!
Deliverance In Jesus' Name
Come out, in the mighty name of Jesus!
You are going.
Come out!
Deliverance In Jesus' Name
In Jesus' name.
You are delivered. Rise up.
Set Free In Jesus' Name
How are you, sir?
I am fine.
What happened to you, sir?
I have never fallen on the ground before. I am a pastor.
I am surprised.
You don’t know what pushed you down?
I don’t know. I know I was sitting upstairs.
I have never fallen down before.
I am surprised.
But now that you have fallen down for the first time in the history of you being a pastor,
what do you have to say?
I think power pass power.
All power belongs to Jesus.
Thank you very much.
But you said something now – you said you are 430 years old and that you are an idol from the family.
Me?
Yes.
I am a pastor. I am just 50 years old. I am not an idol.
You are not 430 years old?
No, I am just 50 years old.
That very demon that was tormenting your life, is out.
Thank you very much.
You are delivered.
Praise the Lord!
Live the rest of your life to please Jesus.
Hallelujah!
God bless you.
Emmanuel!
(God with us - Matthew 1:23)
Praise the Lord!
TESTIMONY TIME
Emmanuel!
(God with us - Matthew 1:23)
Amen.
My name is Pastor Uchechukwu Lukman.
The woman standing beside me is my lovely helpmate.
I am a pastor by calling.
By His grace, I'm an evangelist who is into deliverance ministry.
I grew up in a background that was rooted in idol worship.
When we were growing up, we were taken to the shrine and were given incisions.
Even up to this date, we still have some of those shrines in my father's house.
My father still sacrifices animals to them.
We had those incisions.
When I grew up, things were not working; not just for me alone but for my family,
my immediate siblings and my cousins.
Things were not working out.
There was this barrier of limitation that had always been with those before me -
those who were older than me.
We had been living a life of strife and limitation until eventually, like I said, I gave my life to Christ.
In my family, I became the first born-again Christian after over 400 years.
It was tough growing up in those days; I was disowned by my parents.
I was rejected and cast away by my family.
It was difficult living in my community then as a child of God.
To God be the glory, I did not deny my faith.
I continued.
Until...
I left the church and started working in some other ministries,
moving around, both here and outside the country for evangelical work.
It was not easy – you would minister to people; they would get miracles but they would not remember you.
A lot of them would prosper but they would not remember you.
That had been happening.
I knew that I was from a background of idol worship.
I knew it was a problem and I had gone for counselling.
I had gone to many ministers of God for deliverance and counselling but the thing remained there.
The most agonising thing was
you know, if you are a man of God and you don’t have a settled home,
then you have a problem because you must first of all pastor your house.
But I had a partner who was supposed to be a helpmate but in the background was an enemy
whom the devil was using to work against me.
My lovely wife in those days, before last week, would not greet me, "Good morning".
We lived like that for years.
We didn’t share the same bedroom; we did not eat together.
I did not even eat in the house.
Sometimes, before I went to the altar and picked up the microphone,
I would have my day spoiled and my psyche depressed.
I know what that means as a minister.
It had been a battle until I met some friends who handed a hospitality company over to me.
I began to manage that company as a hospitality business while also doing my pastoral work.
Surprisingly, I would see people who worshipped at The SCOAN come to the company.
They were my customers.
They would come with their problems.
You would see them coming to The SCOAN; when they returned back to the hotel, they would be different.
I saw the case of a particular woman who came to The SCOAN and came back with the Anointing Water.
She used it and before we knew it, my boys called me into the woman's room.
She started excreting a fibroid in the toilet.
We began to wonder what was happening.
It happened that there was a particular case - a friend who was a lodger.
He had a job appointment from one of these oil companies in Bayelsa, Nigeria.
They asked him to do medical tests, which he did.
He came back and was positive to HIV.
After coming to The SCOAN, he came back and he was insisting that I take him to any nearby hospital
so that he could do a test again and confirm his HIV status.
I drove him in my car; we went to Federal Medical Centre for a confirmation test.
I was baffled that the man who initially had a medical report,
stating that he was HIV positive, became negative.
All these things and many other things started happening.
I began to wonder because as a matter of truth and sincerity,
I was one of those men who actually criticized this ministry.
I must tell you that.
On seeing these miracles, I got the tapes of the man of God,
Prophet T.B. Joshua and started listening to them – the audio and video.
I was shocked at the wisdom, the insight into the interpretation of the Word of God.
The miracles moved me but the insight into the Scriptures was amazing.
There are portions of the Scripture that some ministers would not want to dive into and
you would see Prophet T.B. Joshua diving into them, treating them, counselling people on them
and it is wonderful.
He has been a blessing to me; I must tell you that.
Praise the Lord.
This continued and I began to reminisce in my heart; I began to have second thoughts.
I began to have a close study of the ministry.
It encouraged me and I decided that I was going to be a part of this ministry.
Last Sunday was a great day in my life.
I walked into this church and it was awesome when the wise men were going round.
Before Wise Man Daniel got to my row,
I was surprised that I felt some shivering inside of me; I was shaking.
I was wondering what was happening.
I knew I had no malaria parasite.
I began to wonder what was happening and lo and behold,
he placed his hand, first on my chest; it was like a bomb.
I had a ballistic missile explosion.
I was still staggering; I didn’t know what I was doing.
He touched my head again.
Before I knew it, I discovered I was talking but I didn't know what I was saying until
the final deliverance was conducted on me and I became a free man.
SCOAN Testimony
Emmanuel!
[God with us]
After the deliverance that day, I met with the counsellors.
I came here alone; I didn't come with her.
While I was still trying to grasp my movement, whether to be a part of this ministry or not,
I was always asking my wife to be a part so we could come together
but she never wanted to hear anything about The SCOAN.
I was surprised that the day after my deliverance,
my eldest daughter called me while I was still sitting in the church.
She asked, "Daddy, where are you?"
I said, "I am in the church".
She asked, "Which church?"
I said, "I am in The SCOAN".
She said she thought that my deliverance was genuine.
I asked her why she was saying that.
She said, "Mummy has just picked up all your clothes and she is outside washing them".
I was dumbfounded because that had never happened for many years.
When I got home, the following morning when she came to me, she said, "Daddy, good morning, sir".
Initially, I did not know she was the one talking.
She repeated it, "Daddy, I am saying good morning, sir".
I turned and laughed; I was happy.
Since then, she has changed.
I am so happy; I am testifying to that.
The people around me saw that something had just happened to me and my family.
Did you listen to that?
The deliverance that happened to our father affected the wife and everybody around.
Just only one person in the family.
Once a person in the family is delivered, every bondage and chain connected to the family is loosed.
I still have a second testimony that is so astonishing.
I had a family that visited us from Kano.
Their fifteen year old daughter had ran away from home
and for one month, we had been running helter skelter, looking for her.
On the day of my deliverance, after receiving the call from my daughter
that my wife had taken my clothes to wash,
I was surprised that the girl who had never been to Lagos, who doesn’t know anywhere in Lagos,
walked by herself back home on that day.
I am happy, fulfilled and have peace inside of me.
I think I have a brand new marriage now.
SCOAN Testimony
I want to meet and join the family.
We believe you have been inspired by the clip you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe, to witness more of God's power at work in our generation today
and stay up-to-date with the latest prophecies, deliverances, sermons and testimonies
from the Synagogue Church Of All Nations.
Emmanuel TV – changing lives, changing nations and changing the world.
RV - Jacqueline Margaret 21/06/18